based collections वाенное कफ़री कुछ।
All right!
So Lingo.dev is back again
with another hackathon.
So as you might have seen the title
and the thumbnail of this video
Lingo.dev which is an AI powered
localization tool
is again hosting an hackathon
and the best part is
कि हमने पहले भी
बहुँ सारब हागँतों
and बहुती
excited prices
and the best part about
these hackathons
that are hosted by Lingo.dev is
that these are
open-ended hackathons
आप रिधे तर्मिलोक।
कुछ भी बना सकते है, whatever you want, right? The only condition is that you have to use their Lingo.dev tool.
So, before we jump in, before I talk more, let me show you what this hackathon is, how to participate, and most importantly, what prizes are here. So, with that, let's start with the video.
Alright, so you can see that this is the landing page of the hackathon. Link आपको दिस्रिप्शन में मिल जहेंगे. So, this is our second hackathon, जिसका नाम है, Multilingual Hackathon.
and you have a mouse, but उसे पहले, let's see what is this particular thing, okay? What do you have to do? This is the most important thing. You can literally use any tech stack like React, Next.js, Superbase, Node.js, and you have to use Lingo.dev की toolkit.
मतलब की आपके अप्लिकेशन के अंदर, Lingo.dev का कोई भी प्रोड़क्त आपको यूस करना है. It can be Lingo.dev का CLI, it can be your MCP, it can be a compiler, and it can just be a CICD pipeline as well, okay?
So, आपको Lingo.dev के tools को use करना है. Any one tool you can use, or even you can use all the tools, that's up to you. And you have to build something exciting, okay?
Now, what happens is, there is a criteria of evaluating. मतलब, जो यह prices है, यह किस basis पे मिलेंगे. So, there is a criteria कि आपने जो project बनाया है, उसका execution team को अच्छा लगता है, you get 40 points.
अगर team को लगता है कि आपने जो efforts put की है, that is next level, you get 30 points.
अगर आपकी presentation अच्छी है, you get 20 points. And अगर आपका idea बहुत ही unique है, बहुत ही अच्छा है, you get 10 points.
So, you have to try to maximize your points. Okay, आप जितने ज्यादा यहां पर points ले सकते हो, that will help you to win these prizes.
And the prizes are pretty cool. First price, iPad Air, और इस cash equivalent. मतलब, अगर आपको iPad नहीं ची, तो जितने का iPad आप उसका cash ले सकते हैं.
Second price is basically a Sony wireless headphones, okay, और इस cash equivalent. And third price is basically Logitech का MX Master 3S, which is a go-to mouse for every developer. Okay, and again, for cash equivalent.
अगर हम यहां पर और scroll down करते हैं, you will create an empty and a public GitHub repo after the kick-off call.
तो आपके एक kick-off call होगी, एक Zoom meeting के उपर. Don't worry, जब आप इस particular hackathon के अंदर participate करेंगे, you will get all the updates.
And push new commits and you should build. So, आपको बनाना क्या है? It's completely open-ended, मतलब, आप कुछ भी बना सकते हो. The best part, मतलब की creativity आपकी है.
And आपके idea के आपको 10 points मिल रहे हैं.
Okay? Second is, go over our subreddit and see the projects people have built in the past.
So, ये एक inspiration के लिए अच्छा है.
So, अगर आप यहां पर जाते हैं, you can actually see what people have built in their previous tasks.
तीक है? So, आप यहां पर देख सकते हैं वो सारी चीजहे.
I built a real-time video translator with voice learning. Amazing project, right?
वापको बेराद कुछ आइपको बाट नाचा बैने बात बैने हुटेस पूर्ट के बैने हुटे हैं अप हमेशा अपने किसी साइड प्रोजेक्ट पे साइड हैं साइड हुपर काम कर रहे होते हैं और और आपको थे दो टेके टो नेक्स लेवर यू वांड कि वह एक रिगल
तो आपने उस आइडिया को, आप अपने उस प्रोडुक्ट को in hackathons के अंदर लेकर जा सकते हो, you can actually do that particular hackathon, idea in this hackathon, आपको बस लिंगो.dev को यूस करना है, which anyway you have to use, because your application needs an internationalization, तो ये चीज़े आपकी help करते हैं to get a public visibility, and you come to know कि आप कहां stand करते हो, so these open-ended hackathons बहुत कम है market में, so I
to see how good developer you are, how good builder you are, आप community में किस level पर stand करते हो, definitely participate in these, and try कि आपको क्या feedback मिलता है, you will come to know a lot of things about yourself, okay, and plus one more thing, there is a discord link, जो मेने नीचे description में पिन किया है, please make sure to check that out, let me show you what that discord is, and one more thing, please make sure to check out their discord channel, so you have to join their discord link, so that link भी आपको नीचे description में मिल चाहेगा, so
यहां पर आपको सभी announcements, सभी चीज़े यहां पर मिलते रहेंगी, all the updates, for example, यह हमारी पिछली hackathon के updates है, that it has been, submissions are being extended and all, so please make sure that आप इनका discord channel भी जोइन करो, to get all the updates in this particular thing, okay, so this was all about this particular hackathon, so I wish you a very best of luck, once again, it is starting on 16th February, okay, and link आपको यहां पर मिल जाहेंगे, description के दे सभी links है, अगर यह